Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations: an inventory
Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations
- Spectrophotometry, 1933; KG11366.228 (Box 51)
- Computation of Ephemerides, 1904 to 1907; KG11366.229 (Box 51)
- Notes on Orion Cluster, Intensities, B Stars, KG11366.230 (Box 51)
  C.H.L..
  C.H.L. identity uncertain.
- Star Sequences, 1926; KG11366.231 (Box 51)
- RB Standard Star Identifications, KG11366.232 (Box 51)
  Mary L. Miller and J.M.E..
  J.M.E. identity uncertain.
- Chart Plates, 1898 to 1899; KG11366.233 (Box 51)
  Louis D. Wells.
- T Andromedae, 1916; KG11366.234 (Box 51)
  H.C. Wilson.
- Doubtful Variable, Miscellaneous Observations, 1904 to 1912; KG11366.235 (Box 51)
- Pyrheliometer Record, 1916; KG11366.236 (Box 52)
  W..
  W. identity uncertain.
- Pyrheliometer Record, 1917; KG11366.237 (Box 52)
- Variable Star Observations, 1902 to 1903; KG11366.238 (Box 52)
- Variable Star Observations, 1903; KG11366.239 (Box 52)
  Marion F. Michaeli.
- Variable Star Observations, 1904; KG11366.240 (Box 52)
  G.E. Washborn.
- Meridian Photometer, 1907; KG11366.241 (Box 52)
  S.M.P..
  S.M.P. identity uncertain.
- Halley's Comet Observations, 1909; KG11366.242 (Box 52)
- Reductions of Observation for Position, 1909 to 1910; KG11366.243 (Box 52)
  Oliver C. Wendell and Leon Campbell.
- Nova Aquilae, 1918; KG11366.244 (Box 52)
- Comparison Stars, 1906 to 1909; KG11366.245 (Box 52)
- Calculations - Schaer and Others, 1905 to 1911; KG11366.246 (Box 52)
- 24-in reflector journal, 1907; KG11366.247 (Box 52)
- Plates, Photometers, 1935 to 1936; KG11366.248 (Box 52)
  J.E. Jones.
- RH Plates - Photometry, 1933; KG11366.249 (Box 52)
  Also identified as: 94.
- Variable Observations, 1907 to 1908; KG11366.250 (Box 52)
- SV Tauri, 1925; KG11366.251 (Box 52)
  C. Lanousyk.
  C. Lanousyk identity uncertain.
- Observations, 1909; KG11366.252 (Box 52)
  Samuel C. Catteral.
- Meridian Photometer, 1908; KG11366.253 (Box 52)
- Jupiter Eclipses and Variable Stars, 1898; KG11366.254 (Box 52)
- Jupiter Eclipses and Variable Stars, 1899; KG11366.255 (Box 52)
- New Variables, 1926 to 1928; KG11366.256 (Box 53)
- Evening Cloud Record, 1916 to 1917; KG11366.257 (Box 53)
- Shade Glasses, 1902 to 1903; KG11366.258 (Box 53)
  C.M. Olmsted.
- Pole Plates (MC) and Misc. Experiments, KG11366.259 (Box 53)
  F. Schilt.
- Photometric Experiments, 1929; KG11366.260 (Box 53)
- Variable Star Observations, Photometry, 1929; KG11366.261 (Box 53)
- Variable Star Observations, Photometry, 1929; KG11366.262 (Box 53)
- Variable Star Observations, Photometry, 1929; KG11366.263 (Box 53)
- Variable Star Observations, Photometry, 1929; KG11366.264 (Box 53)
- Variable Star Observations, Photometry, 1929; KG11366.265 (Box 53)
- Variable Star Observations, Photometry, 1929; KG11366.266 (Box 53)
- Variable Star Observations, Photometry, 1929; KG11366.267 (Box 53)
- Variable Star Observations, Photometry, 1929; KG11366.268 (Box 53)
  Also identified as: 71.
- Variable Star Observations, Photometry, 1929; KG11366.269 (Box 53)
  Also identified as: 72.
- Variable Star Observations, Photometry, 1929; KG11366.270 (Box 53)
  Also identified as: 73.
- Variable Star Observations, Photometry, 1930; KG11366.271 (Box 53)
  Also identified as: 74.
- Variable Star Observations, Photometry, 1930; KG11366.272 (Box 53)
  Also identified as: 75.
- RH Plates, 1930; KG11366.273 (Box 53)
  Also identified as: 76.
- RH Plates, 1930; KG11366.274 (Box 53)
  Also identified as: 77.
- RH Plates, 1930; KG11366.275 (Box 53)
  Also identified as: 78.
- RH Plates, 1930; KG11366.276 (Box 54)
  Also identified as: 79.
- RH Plates, 1930 to 1931; KG11366.277 (Box 54)
  Also identified as: 80.
- RH Plates, 1931; KG11366.278 (Box 54)
- RH Plates, 1931; KG11366.279 (Box 54)
- RH Plates, 1931; KG11366.280 (Box 54)
- RH Plates, 1931 to 1932; KG11366.281 (Box 54)
  Also identified as: 84.
- RH Plates, 1932; KG11366.282 (Box 54)
  Also identified as: 85.
- RH Plates PTM, 1932; KG11366.283 (Box 54)
  Also identified as: 86.
- RH Plates PTM, 1932; KG11366.284 (Box 54)
  Also identified as: 87.
- RH Plates PTM, 1932; KG11366.285 (Box 54)
  Also identified as: 88.
- RH Plates PTM, 1932; KG11366.286 (Box 54)
  Also identified as: 89.
- RH Plates PTM, 1932; KG11366.287 (Box 54)
  Also identified as: 90.
- RH Plates PTM, 1932 to 1933; KG11366.288 (Box 54)
  Also identified as: 91.
- RH Plates PTM, 1933 to 1934; KG11366.289 (Box 54)
  Also identified as: 92.
- RH Plates PTM, 1933; KG11366.290 (Box 54)
  Also identified as: 93.
- RH Plates PTM, 1933; KG11366.291 (Box 54)
  Also identified as: 95.
- RH Plates PTM, 1933 to 1934; KG11366.292 (Box 54)
- RH Plates PTM, 1934; KG11366.293 (Box 54)
- RH Plates PTM, 1934; KG11366.294 (Box 54)
- RH Plates PTM, 1934; KG11366.295 (Box 55)
- Equatorial Observations, 1877; KG11366.296 (Box 55)
- Equator Points, Meridian Observations, 1877; KG11366.297 (Box 55)
- Telescope Observations, 1878; KG11366.298 (Box 55)
- Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1878; KG11366.299 (Box 55)
  Also labeled as R45.
- Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1878; KG11366.300 (Box 55)
  Also labeled as R47.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1878; KG11366.301 (Box 55)
  Also labeled as R48. See 11365.481 for an R46.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1878 to 1879; KG11366.302 (Box 55)
  Also labeled as R50.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1879; KG11366.303 (Box 55)
  Also labeled as R51.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1879; KG11366.304 (Box 55)
  Also labeled as R54.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1879; KG11366.305 (Box 55)
  Also labeled as R55.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1879 to 1880; KG11366.306 (Box 55)
  Also labeled as R91.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1880; KG11366.307 (Box 55)
  Also labeled as R92.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1880; KG11366.308 (Box 55)
  Also labeled as R93.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1880 to 1881; KG11366.309 (Box 55)
  Also labeled as R95.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1881; KG11366.310 (Box 55)
  Also labeled as R96.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1881; KG11366.311 (Box 55)
  Also labeled as R98.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1881; KG11366.312 (Box 55)
  Hersch G. Wobb.
  Also labeled as R99.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1882; KG11366.313 (Box 55)
  Also labeled as R103.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1882 to 1883; KG11366.314 (Box 55)
  Also labeled as R104.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1883; KG11366.315 (Box 55)
  Also labeled as R107.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1884; KG11366.316 (Box 55)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1885; KG11366.317 (Box 55)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1885 to 1897; KG11366.318 (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1885 to 1886; KG11366.319 (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1886 to 1887; KG11366.320 (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1888; KG11366.321a (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1888; KG11366.321b (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1888; KG11366.322a (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1888 to 1889; KG11366.322b (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1889; KG11366.323 (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1889; KG11366.324 (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1889 to 1890; KG11366.325 (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1891; KG11366.326 (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1891; KG11366.327 (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1891 to 1892; KG11366.328 (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1893; KG11366.329 (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1893; KG11366.330 (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1894; KG11366.331 (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1895; KG11366.332 (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1895; KG11366.333 (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1895; KG11366.334 (Box 56)
  See KG 11365.531-.533.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1896; KG11366.335 (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1896; KG11366.336 (Box 56)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1896; KG11366.337 (Box 57)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1896; KG11366.338 (Box 57)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1897; KG11366.339 (Box 57)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1897; KG11366.340 (Box 57)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1897; KG11366.341 (Box 57)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1897; KG11366.342 (Box 57)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1897; KG11366.343 (Box 57)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1897; KG11366.344 (Box 57)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1897; KG11366.345 (Box 57)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1898; KG11366.346 (Box 57)
  See KG 11365.539.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1898; KG11366.347 (Box 57)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1898; KG11366.348 (Box 57)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1898; KG11366.349 (Box 57)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1898; KG11366.350 (Box 57)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1898; KG11366.351 (Box 57)
  Also identified as: 100.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1898; KG11366.352 (Box 57)
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1898; KG11366.353 (Box 57)
  Also identified as: 102.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1898; KG11366.354 (Box 57)
  Also identified as: 103.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1899; KG11366.355 (Box 57)
  Also identified as: 104.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1899; KG11366.356 (Box 57)
  Also identified as: 105.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1899; KG11366.357 (Box 58)
  Also identified as: 106.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1899; KG11366.358 (Box 58)
  Also identified as: 107.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1899; KG11366.359 (Box 58)
  Also identified as: 108.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1899; KG11366.360 (Box 58)
  Also identified as: 109.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1899; KG11366.361 (Box 58)
  Also identified as: 110.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1899; KG11366.362 (Box 58)
  Also identified as: 111.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1899; KG11366.363 (Box 58)
  Also identified as: 112.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1900; KG11366.364 (Box 58)
  Also identified as: 113.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1900; KG11366.365 (Box 58)
  Also identified as: 114.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1900; KG11366.366 (Box 58)
  Also identified as: 115.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1900; KG11366.367 (Box 58)
  Also identified as: 116.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1900; KG11366.368 (Box 58)
  Also identified as: 117.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1900; KG11366.369 (Box 58)
  Also identified as: 118.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1900; KG11366.370 (Box 58)
  Also identified as: 119.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1900; KG11366.371 (Box 58)
  Also identified as: 120.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1900 to 1901; KG11366.372 (Box 58)
  Also identified as: 121.
- Chronograph Record, Zone Stars, 24-in, 1877; KG11366.373 (Box 58)
  Continued in KG11365.545.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1901; KG11366.374 (Box 58)
  Also identified as: 124.
- Variable Star Observations, Reduction of Photometric Observations, 1901; KG11366.375 (Box 58)
  Also identified as: 125.
- General Catalog, Circle Readings, 1871 to 1872; KG11366.376 (Box 58)
- General Catalog, Circle Readings, 1871 to 1872; KG11366.377 (Box 58)
- General Catalog, Circle Readings, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.378 (Box 59)
- Polar Catalog, Circle Readings, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.379 (Box 59)
- Polar Catalog, Circle Readings, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.380 (Box 59)
- Polar Catalog, Circle Readings, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.381 (Box 59)
- General Catalog, Circle Readings, 1874 to 1875; KG11366.382 (Box 59)
- General Catalog, Circle Readings, 1874 to 1875; KG11366.383 (Box 59)
- General Catalog, Circle Readings, 1874 to 1875; KG11366.384 (Box 59)
- General Catalog, Circle Readings, 1874 to 1875; KG11366.385 (Box 59)
- General Catalog, Circle Readings, 1874 to 1875; KG11366.386 (Box 59)
- General Catalog, Circle Readings, 1874 to 1875; KG11366.387 (Box 59)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1876; KG11366.388 (Box 59)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1876; KG11366.389 (Box 59)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1877; KG11366.390 (Box 59)
- Maskelyne Fundamental Stars, Circle Readins, 1877; KG11366.391 (Box 59)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1877; KG11366.392 (Box 59)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1878; KG11366.393 (Box 59)
- Circle Readings, Coast Survey Catalog, 1878; KG11366.394 (Box 59)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1879; KG11366.395 (Box 59)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1879; KG11366.396 (Box 59)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1879; KG11366.397 (Box 59)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1879; KG11366.398 (Box 59)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1879 to 1880; KG11366.399 (Box 59)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1880; KG11366.400 (Box 59)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1880; KG11366.401 (Box 60)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1880; KG11366.402 (Box 60)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1880; KG11366.403 (Box 60)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1880 to 1881; KG11366.404 (Box 60)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1881; KG11366.405 (Box 60)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1881; KG11366.406 (Box 60)
- Fundamental Stars, Observations, 1881; KG11366.407 (Box 60)
- Fundamental Stars, Observations, 1881 to 1883; KG11366.408 (Box 60)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1883; KG11366.409 (Box 60)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1883; KG11366.410 (Box 60)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1883; KG11366.411 (Box 60)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1883; KG11366.412 (Box 60)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1883 to 1884; KG11366.413 (Box 60)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1884; KG11366.414 (Box 60)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1884 to 1885; KG11366.415 (Box 60)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1885; KG11366.416 (Box 60)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1885 to 1886; KG11366.417 (Box 60)
- Circle Readings, Fundamental Stars for Zone, 1877; KG11366.418 (Box 60)
  Also identified as: B1?.
- Observations for Inclination of Declimation Wire, 1878 to 1879; KG11366.419 (Box 60)
- Polaris Circle Readings and Observations, 1879; KG11366.420 (Box 60)
- Polaris Circle Readings and Observations, 1879 to 1880; KG11366.421 (Box 60)
- Polaris Circle Readings and Observations, 1880; KG11366.422 (Box 60)
- Polaris Circle Readings and Observations, 1880 to 1881; KG11366.423 (Box 61)
- Polaris Circle Readings and Observations, 1881 to 1882; KG11366.424 (Box 61)
- Polaris Circle Readings and Observations, 1883 to 1884; KG11366.425 (Box 61)
- Polaris Circle Readings and Observations, 1884; KG11366.426 (Box 61)
- Zone Measurements, 1882; KG11366.427 (Box 61)
- Revision of equatorial zone, 1883; KG11366.428 (Box 61)
- Revision of equatorial zone, 1883; KG11366.429 (Box 61)
- Revision of equatorial zone, 1883; KG11366.430 (Box 61)
- Revision of equatorial zone, 1883; KG11366.431 (Box 61)
- Revision of equatorial zone, 1883; KG11366.432 (Box 61)
- Fundamental Stars for zones, 1870 to 1871; KG11366.433 (Box 61)
  A. McConnel and W.S.R..
  W.S.R. identity uncertain.
- Fundamental Stars for zones, 1871; KG11366.434 (Box 61)
- Fundamental Stars for zones, 1871; KG11366.435 (Box 61)
- Fundamental Stars for zones, 1871; KG11366.436 (Box 61)
- Fundamental Stars for zones, 1872; KG11366.437 (Box 61)
- Fundamental Stars for zones, 1872; KG11366.438 (Box 61)
- Fundamental Stars for zones, 1872; KG11366.439 (Box 61)
- Fundamental Stars for zones, 1870 to 1871; KG11366.440 (Box 61)
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, KG11366.441 (Box 61)
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, KG11366.442 (Box 61)
  Also identified as: F12.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, KG11366.443 (Box 61)
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1871 to 1872; KG11366.444 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F14.
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1871; KG11366.445 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F15.
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1871 to 1872; KG11366.446 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F16.
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1871; KG11366.447 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F17.
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1871 to 1872; KG11366.448 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F18.
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1871 to 1872; KG11366.449 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F19.
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1871 to 1872; KG11366.450 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F20.
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1871 to 1872; KG11366.451 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F21.
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1872; KG11366.452 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F22.
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1872; KG11366.453 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F23.
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, KG11366.454 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F24.
- Polar Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.455 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F26.
- Polar Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.456 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F27.
- Polar Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.457 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F28.
- Polar Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.458 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F29.
- Polar Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.459 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F30.
- Polar Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.460 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F31.
- Polar Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.461 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F32.
- Polar Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.462 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F33.
- Polar Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.463 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F34.
- Polar Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.464 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F35.
- Polar Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.465 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F36.
- Polar Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1874 to 1875; KG11366.466 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F37.
- Polar Catalog Observations and Reductions, KG11366.467 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F38.
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1874 to 1875; KG11366.468 (Box 62)
  Also identified as: F39.
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, KG11366.469 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F40.
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1874 to 1875; KG11366.470 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F41.
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1874 to 1875; KG11366.471 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F42.
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1874 to 1875; KG11366.472 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F43.
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1874 to 1875; KG11366.473 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F44.
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1874 to 1875; KG11366.474 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F45.
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1874 to 1875; KG11366.475 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F46.
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1874 to 1875; KG11366.476 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F47.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1876 to 1877; KG11366.477 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F48.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1876 to 1877; KG11366.478 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F49.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1876 to 1877; KG11366.479 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F50.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1876 to 1877; KG11366.480 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F51.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1876 to 1877; KG11366.481 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F52.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1876 to 1877; KG11366.482 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F53.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1877; KG11366.483 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F54.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1877; KG11366.484 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F55.
- Maskelyne Fundamentals, 1877; KG11366.485 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F56.
- Meridian Circle, 1875; KG11366.486 (Box 63)
- Maskelyne Fundamentals, 1877; KG11366.487 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F57.
- Fundamental Stars, 1878; KG11366.488 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F59.
- Fundamental Stars, 1878; KG11366.489 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F60.
- Fundamental Stars, 1878; KG11366.490 (Box 63)
  Also identified as: F61.
- Fundamental Stars, 1878; KG11366.491 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F62.
- Coast Survey Catalog, 1878; KG11366.492 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F63.
- Coast Survey Catalog, 1878; KG11366.493 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F64.
- Coast Survey Catalog, 1878; KG11366.494 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F65.
- Miscellaneous Stars, 1878; KG11366.495 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F66.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1878; KG11366.496 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F67.